<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2448_Report_pg46">

    <head> Ref: <eventName>Bentwaters Incident</eventName>, <year>1980</year>
        <organization org="MoD">Ministry of Defence</organization> Main Building Whitehall <location
            loc="London">London</location> SWLA Telephone(Direct Dialling) 01-218-[] (Switchboard)
        01-218-9000 </head>

    <address> Dear [], </address>

    <body> As you know, <organization org="OSI">OSI</organization> has completed a report on the
            <ufoDesc>landing of a craft of unknown origin crewed by several entities</ufoDesc> near
            <eventLocation eloc="Raf_Bentwaters">RAF Bentwaters</eventLocation> on the <weather>night</weather> of the
            <eventDate date="12/29/1980">December 29/30 1980</eventDate>. Interestingly,
            <organization org="OSI">OSI</organization> reports that the <ufoDesc>entities were
            approximately 1 ½ meters tall, wearing what appeared to be nylon coated pressure suits,
            but no helmets</ufoDesc>. <weather>Conditions on the night were misty</weather>,
        giving the appearance that the entities were hovering above ground level. <event>Tape recordings
        were made on which the entities are heard to speak in an electronically synthesised version
        of English, with a strong American accent</event>. Similar transmissions intercepted irregularly by
        ISA(?) since 1973(see attachment- Flag 1). According to <organization org="OSI"
            >OSI</organization>, <alienDesc>entities had claw-like hands and with three fingers and
            an opposable thumb</alienDesc>. Despite original reports(Flags 3- 0), <organization
            org="OSI">OSI</organization> said <ufoDesc>the craft was not damaged but landed deliberately as
        part of a series of visits</ufoDesc> to <organization org="SAC">SAC</organization> bases in USA and Europe. <event>Reports that craft was repaired
        by US serviceman or was taken on to the base are not confirmed</event> by <organization org="OSI"
            >OSI</organization>. <event>Landing is not considered a defence issue in view of the
            overt peaceful nature of the contact</event>, but investigations by [] are to be
        continued on [] authority. Precautionary plans for counter-information at a local level
        involving [] and [] is strongly recommended. </body>


    <signature>Sincerely []</signature>


</report>
