<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2449_Report_pg225">

    <head> From: [] Sent: 26 June 2008 14:29 To:[] Subject: <eventName>TERN HILL
            SIGHTING</eventName>
        <eventDate date="06/07/2008">7 JUNE 2008</eventDate>
    </head>

    <body> The Sun has reported a UFO sighting over <eventLocation
            eloc="Temhill_Barracks">Temhill Barracks</eventLocation> in <location loc="Shropshire"
            >Shropshire</location> at about <weather>11pm</weather> on 7 June
            2008. It appears that a number of soldiers saw <ufoDesc>lights in the sky</ufoDesc> and made a
        video which they have passed to the newspaper. They have not made a formal written report on
        the matter, although they did inform their superiors. The <organization org="MoD"
            >MoD</organization> in <location loc="London">London</location> became involved when the
        press office was contacted by the newspaper on 24th June. On 25th June I requested a copy of
        the video from <organization org="MOGQ">Media Ops at HQ 5 Div</organization> where it had been passed by the unit concerned. It
        shows a number of lights in the sky. As reported in the paper, <ufoDesc>the lights change
            colour and appear square, but this looks like the pixels snag up as the photographer
            zoomed in. They do not appear to be moving vary quickly</ufoDesc>. The <organization org="BBC">BBC</organization> has reported
        that at the same time as the alleged incident, <event>a local hotel was lighting off Chinese
        lanterns and, apparently, the hotel manager thinks the whole UFO story is “highly
        hilarious”</event>. I do not intend to investigate any further as I think we have our answer and, as
        I suspect there might be copyright issues surrounding the video, do not intend to retain a
        copy on our files. I will inform the soldiers of my decision through their 2ic. </body>

    <signature>[] DAS-FOI []</signature>

</report>
