<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2452_pg156">

    <head> </head>

    <body> Firstly I must stress that <event>I am one of the world’s biggest sceptics when it come
            to UFO’s</event> however I can offer no realistic explanation for what I saw, therefore
        it was literally an unidentified flying object. I was working in the air traffic control at
            <eventName>RAF Lyneham</eventName> in <eventLocation eloc="Whillshire"
            >Willshire</eventLocation> on <weather>night shift</weather>. I was the approach
        controller and supervisor of the shirt. At the time I must have had almost 20 years of
        working on radar and was very used to analyzing the quirks which a radar can produce such as
        bird activity, ananprop (atmospheric variation) and MTI suppression. I was recovering a
        couple of C130’s to base when I saw a <ufoDesc>large “blob”</ufoDesc> on the radar screen
        about 3 miles from touchdown on the center line. I had no idea what it was so I called it to
        the pilots and fed them around it. <ufoDesc>The blob was stationary</ufoDesc>. I handed the
        aircraft over to the visual controller and then went upstairs to the visual control room
        where I could see <ufoDesc>the “blob”</ufoDesc> on the DFTI (distance from touchdown
        indicator). I looked through the window but couldn’t see anything, so I returned to the
        radar room. <ufoDesc>Suddenly the “blob” burst and fragmented shooting off in all directions
            at massive speed</ufoDesc>. Some discussion took place between me and the visual
        controller and we left it at that. <event>Sometime later I received a phone call from a very
            agitated airman</event> who said “Sir I have not been drinking, I am on guard duty and
        have just seen something that was very strange, and I can’t explain but thought the Air
        traffic controller should be informed of. He said he had seen a <ufoDesc>bright
            light</ufoDesc> to the east I remember commenting that it was nearly Christmas but
        doubted that we would find 3 wise men or a virgin at <location loc="Lyneham"
            >Lyneham</location>. He said that the <ufoDesc>bright light had burst and that fragments
            had shot in all directions at speeds which he could not believe</ufoDesc>. He said he
        had <ufoDesc>never seen anything travel so fast and it was definitely not an
            aircraft</ufoDesc>. <event>His account caused the hairs on my neck to stand up</event>.
            <event>Several minutes later another airman telephoned and gave a similar
            account.</event> I logged all the details and telephoned the MOD UFO desk, gave them a
        verbal report backed up with a written report which hopefully they will still have on
        record. This happened just before Christmas but I struggle top remember the year. I served
        at <location loc="Lyneham">Lyneham</location> in the early to mid <year>90’s</year> and I
        guess it would be <eventDate date="12/24/1995">December of 1994 or 1995</eventDate>. I Think
        the visual controller was a chap called [] who was a Sergeant at the time because I cannot
        justify or explain it any better than I have to you. Please call me on my mobile if you
        would like to discuss it more. [] </body>


    <signature>Formley Flight Lieutenant, RAF </signature>

</report>
