<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2452_pg6">

    <head>From: [] Sent: <eventDate date="11/01/2009">01 November 2009</eventDate> 01:37 To: Air CmdSecCS-UFO Desk1 Subject: <eventName>large
            sighting</eventName>
    </head>

    <address>Dear Sir</address>

    <body> I have just seen six UFOS whilst driving home. I am sure there is a good explanation and
        would like to check if you had military craft on exercise in the area to this number. At
        12:31 this evening, approx half an hour ago I saw <ufoDesc>6 lights almost in an S
            shape</ufoDesc>
        <event>slowly moving across the sky</event>. I was on the road FROM <location
            loc="Humberston">Humberston</location> (suburb of Cleethorpes) to Tetnoy, North East
        Lines. I was on the straight just before Tetnoy villaqe when I saw through my cars front
        window these 6 lights. I’ve never seen anything like them, it just looked very odd. I pulled
        over and got out to look further. <event>They were moving in formation from West to north
            east {towards the sea)</event>. The conditions were <weather>misty in the sky</weather>,
        although at <weather>ground level it was clear</weather>. Then <event>one of the lights
            disappeared quickly</event>. I got back into the car to follow the lights and pulled
        over again further along. Only two lights remained and gradually faded out. I would like to
        note that <ufoDesc>there was NO sound</ufoDesc>. I would like this to be anonymous, you are
        welcome to contact me discreetly but I do not want the media to know of me or my name as I
        run several businesses and have a reputation to oonsider. I have taken several photographs
        on my phone but can not examine them or blow them up until I get back into office as I have
        left cable there. I would appreciate knowing if you had six helicopters in the area at this
        time or have I seen a genuine UFO formation? </body>

    <signature>Many thanks []</signature>



</report>
