<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2454_pg246">

    <head>Sent: <eventDate date="01/13/2009">13 January 2009</eventDate> 15:31 To: Alr CmdSecCS-UFO
        Desk Subject: <eventName>Strange sighting</eventName> [RESTRICTED] Classification:
        RESTRICTED</head>
    <address>Dear Sir/ Madam,</address>
    <body>Please forgive me if I have your information wrong. I have been given advice from a
        colleague of mine to contact yourself. This was not reported to Police per say but I thought
        I ought to let you know as I saw it. <event>I have been a serving Police Officer for a
            number of years now and my Partner Karl Norman</event> who was with me at the time is an
        ex serviceman in the <organization org="RAF">RAF</organization>. I was at my friends address
        in <eventLocation eloc="Birghtlingsea_Essex">Brightlingsea, Essex</eventLocation> on New
        Years Eve seeing in the New Year, just before <weather>midnight</weather> myself and my
        partner were in the back garden having a cigarette; <event>I could hear fireworks in the
            distance</event> so looked up to see it I could see them. <ufoDesc>In the sky was a
            bright orange/yellow light</ufoDesc> at first glance <event>I Ignored it thinking it was
            a trailing firework</event> but then double took as it did not disappear. My immediate
        thought was we are near water and perhaps that could explain the <ufoDesc>light</ufoDesc>
        but it still did not disappear, <ufoDesc>it moved very slowly in like a half circle around
            the top of us</ufoDesc> then <ufoDesc>stopped over the water</ufoDesc> between <location
            loc="Brightingsea_Essex">Brightingsea and East Mersea</location>. It was <ufoDesc>quite
            large</ufoDesc> and the <weather>night was extremely clear with no clouds or
            mist</weather>. I would hazard a guess about <ufoDesc>1500 to 2000 feet up</ufoDesc>.
            <ufoDesc>It stayed perfectly still for about 3-4 minutes then appeared to shoot straight
            up in the air very fast, going completely out of view in less then 30 seconds</ufoDesc>,
            <event>I must be honest I stood there a bit in awe and missed the start of the new year
            because of it</event>. In fact I even called my friends daughter to see it! It may be
        completely trivial to you and you may even press the delete button, but after a few days of
        wondering whether I was seeing things I saw the news about the Lincoln sightings and damage
        to the wind turbine I could have fallen off my seat it was very similar to what I saw New
        years eve. With Karl being ex <organization org="RAF">RAF</organization> I asked him quite
        innocently what it was and he was as disturbed as I was with no answer! I would not have
        bothered you with it in all honesty but having it play on my mind a few days I thought you
        were the best people to make the decision about whether it was worth your time or not. If
        you have any questions or queries I will be happy to assist in any way possible. My work
        contact details are attached to the bottom of this email, my personal Telephone numbers are
        as follows: Tel:[]</body>
    <signature>Many thanks for your time, []</signature>




</report>
