<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2456_pg234">

    <head>M.O.D. Main Building Whitehall Annan Dumfriesshire London Section4 13-07-09 UFO Sightings
        since 1996 -2009</head>
    <address>Dear Sir</address>
    <body>On the above heading is what I've seen, spotted over the years some I've takes photo's as
        well as videos of some from 2007 1st June 20007 & 2008 plus others in the past few weeks
        which I've made it public in the local paper. Some of the LFO'S which you can just make
        their shape out, but the one I took in 2007 when videoed it took less than 6 of second to
        enter & disappear when it buzzed this old WWIl tempest plane in the area of Dornock town &
        Fastriggs, the other outside my back garden when I videoed an RAF jet circling the area
        several times before I went out with my camera which was a cold cloudy day, when I started
        to video the jet at the same time this UFO just popped out from behind a cloud going all
        over the place & back into the clouds them there were others doing the same but only two of
        them just kept popping in & out of the clouds while the rest just stayed behind thin layers
        of the clouds I could just make out. All the others were taken by different cameras I have &
        one that struck me the most of all when I did not have my camera then bat I watched it for
        about 20 minutes it was all black, no port windows, no strobe lights, no sign of where the
        engines were as one would on any air craft, no sound at all very quiet, but underneath was
        what struck me most of all? This UFO, would be about 40/60 feet circular the height from the
        bottom of the UFO to the top part about 15/20 if no more? Underneath this craft had two
        different shaped type boxes then all the arca of it had earth military type camouflage we
        use on all vehicles & planes, it was about 500/1060fect above me & it just look like a giant
        Frisbee! This was August 1996 Sunday A very clear blue sky it was 1:15pm, once I got home I
        made a model of it and made a rough birds eye view of it's path as it went over the Solway
        cost over into England towards the East coast? I keep a kind of record of them so that I can
        keep track & numbers I've seen & caught on my cameras over the years. I'm not on the
        internet or other nets, as I can't afford the cost or a decent PC, hat do my best with I
        have, though I have been interested in UFO'S since my school days & would like to know how
        far back the UK M.O,D., has known of these space crafts that keep popping in & out of our
        planet buzzing our aircrafts or just floating over at a slow speed which you can pick out
        all the details but don't disappear or change shape. I had two silver orbs on video one
        taken at the solway coast & above my house tie latest I got was the last week of May 2009
        while photographing two jets going in different directions when I saw 3 large spaceships but
        managed to get all on my SLR camera but 2of them when blown up look like battle ships from
        Star Wars Film its on cunning with the shape they are! To me they are the mother of all
        space crafts I've ever seen. What I hope if possible, of a list of' these crafts since seen
        & reported in our country to date plus any true videos/films &photos of these crafts as I
        would like to remake all my cuttings & information of magazines in order of date de lime of
        year. I'm X- RAF, ARIR &R.O.C. Look forward to hearing from</body>
    <signature>Yours faithfully</signature>


</report>
