<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2456_pg234">

    <head>M.O.D. Main Building Whitehall Annan <location loc="Dumfriesshire_London">Dumfriesshire
            London</location> Section4 13-07-09 <eventName>UFO Sightings since 1996
            -2009</eventName></head>
    <address>Dear Sir</address>
    <body>On the above heading is what I've seen, spotted over the years some I've takes photo's as
        well as videos of some from <eventDate date="06/01/2007">2007 1st June 20007 and
            2008</eventDate> plus others in the past few weeks which I've made it public in the
        local paper. Some of the UFO'S which you can just make their shape out, but the one I took
        in 2007 when videoed <ufoDesc>it took less than 6 of second to enter and disappear when it
            buzzed this old WWIl tempest plane</ufoDesc> in the area of Dornock town and Fastriggs,
        the other outside my back garden when I videoed an <organization org="RAF"
            >RAF</organization> jet circling the area several times before I went out with my camera
        which was a <weather>cold cloudy day</weather>, when I started to video the jet at the same
        time this <ufoDesc>UFO just popped out from behind a cloud going all over the place and back
            into the clouds them there were others doing the same but only two of them just kept
            popping in and out of the clouds while the rest just stayed behind thin layers of the
            clouds I could just make out</ufoDesc>. All the others were taken by different cameras I
        have and one that struck me the most of all when I did not have my camera then bat <event>I
            watched it for about 20 minutes</event>
        <ufoDesc>it was all black, no port windows, no strobe lights, no sign of where the engines
            were as one would on any air craft, no sound at all very quiet</ufoDesc>, but underneath
        was what struck me most of all? This UFO, would be about<ufoDesc> 40/60 feet circular the
            height from the bottom of the UFO to the top part about 15/20</ufoDesc> if no
            more?<ufoDesc> Underneath this craft had two different shaped type boxes then all the
            arca of it had earth military type camouflage we use on all vehicles and
            planes</ufoDesc>, <ufoDesc>it was about 500/1000feet above me and it just look like a
            giant Frisbe</ufoDesc>e! This was August 1996 Sunday <weather>A very clear blue sky it
            was 1:15pm</weather>, once I got home I made a model of it and made a rough birds eye
        view of it's path as it went over the Solway cost over into England towards the East coast?
        I keep a kind of record of them so that I can keep track and numbers I've seen and caught on
        my cameras over the years. I'm not on the internet or other nets, as I can't afford the cost
        or a decent PC, had do my best with I have, though I have been interested in UFO'S since my
        school days and would like to know how far back the UK M.O,D., has known of these space
        crafts that keep popping in and out of our planet buzzing our aircrafts or just floating
        over at a slow speed which you can pick out all the details but don't disappear or change
        shape. I had <ufoDesc>two silver orbs</ufoDesc> on video one taken at the solway coast and
        above my house tie latest I got was the last week of May 2009 while photographing two jets
        going in different directions when I saw<ufoDesc> 3 large spaceships</ufoDesc> but managed
        to get all on my SLR camera but 2of them when blown up <ufoDesc>look like battle ships from
            Star Wars Film its on cunning with the shape</ufoDesc> they are! To me they are the
            <ufoDesc>mother of all space crafts</ufoDesc> I've ever seen. What I hope if possible,
        of a list of' these crafts since seen and reported in our country to date plus any true
        videos/films and photos of these crafts as I would like to remake all my cuttings and
        information of magazines in order of date de lime of year. I'm X- <organization org="RAF"
            >RAF</organization>, <organization org="ARIR">ARIR</organization> and <organization
            org="ROC">R.O.C.</organization> Look forward to hearing from</body>
    <signature>Yours faithfully</signature>


</report>
