<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2459_Report_pg44">
    <head><eventDate date="02/23/2009">22:52 23 February 2009</eventDate></head>
    <address>Dear Sir/Madam,</address>
    <body>I live by <eventLocation eloc="WaterLoo">Waterloo, London</eventLocation>, on a 10th floor
        flat overlooking a substantial part of the southern part of the city. <event>I have become quite
        perturbed over the past couple of nights by UFO's</event>, of which I believe that I have seen
            <ufoDesc>3 of varying sizes</ufoDesc>. My profession is of that of a CEO of two
        companies listed on the stockmarket, so i think myself to be a sensible and sane individual.
        The sightings involve <ufoDesc>one object with a white light and alternating red lights at
            an angle</ufoDesc>. The object came from south-east London, headed toward
            <eventName>Canary Wharf</eventName>,<ufoDesc> stopped in mid air</ufoDesc>, at which
        point <ufoDesc>an alternating sequence of red lights flashed at a 180 degree angle</ufoDesc>
        with <ufoDesc>the top light being on the left hand side of the object</ufoDesc> with the
        <event>lights moving down</event> toward the bottom right of the angle, before the <ufoDesc>lights switched
            side instantaneously and the object went back toward south-east</ufoDesc> London.
        Roughly <ufoDesc>one minute later the object returned in my direction</ufoDesc>,
            <ufoDesc>the red lights continuing to lash alongside it</ufoDesc>, before <event>it headed
        north over my apartment and out of sight</event>. My most recent sighting took place at
            <weather>22:52</weather> tonight, 23 February 2009. This sighting occurred for four
        seconds, and was <ufoDesc>the flashing of a huge object taking up a portion of the sky the
            size</ufoDesc> of which I have never seen before. <ufoDesc>It appeared to be flying
            low</ufoDesc>, and had, as I recall, <ufoDesc>three lights</ufoDesc>, of which one I
        believe was a <ufoDesc>normal white light, and the other two were green lights</ufoDesc>.
            <ufoDesc>It vanished out of my sight almost immediately</ufoDesc>, and I was unable to
        track the lights. If you are able to shed light on either of these two incidents I would be
        most grateful. <event>I do not proclaim to be an expert in helicopters, but am able to spot one
        from my window with ease normally</event>.</body>
    <signature> Many thanks. Yours Faithfully, []</signature>
</report>
