<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2459_pg121">
    <head>05/02/2009</head>
    <address> Dear Sir / Madam,</address>
    <body> Whilst driving along <eventName>Wolstanton Road</eventName>, <eventLocation
            eloc="Chesterton_Newcastle">Chesterton, Newcastle</eventLocation> Under Lyme at
            <weather>18:32</weather> on <eventDate date="04/02/2009">04/02/2009</eventDate> I
        noticed an <ufoDesc>orange light fairly low in the sky</ufoDesc>. At first I thought it was
        a street light but then realised that it was too high in the sky. It was a <ufoDesc>dullish
            orange colour</ufoDesc> and what made me think it strange was that <ufoDesc>it was
            approximately 15-20 times larger than a normal star but at the same time not as
            bright</ufoDesc>. <event>I also knew it was not Venus as that is visible in another part
            of the sky</event>. The<ufoDesc> object was circular in shape but did not have a defined
            edge</ufoDesc> and <ufoDesc>its surface appeared to have movement or texture much like a
            small section of the suns surface but infinately dimmer</ufoDesc>. <event>I pulled over
            in my car and pointed the object out to my two children</event> [] and []. [] asked me
        what it was to which I could only tell her that <ufoDesc>it might be a fireball</ufoDesc> as
        I had heard of these in the press and [] asked 'what's the <ufoDesc>orange round thing in
            the sky</ufoDesc>'. <event>I grabbed my mobile phone and tried to take a photo of the
            object but it did not appear on the photo</event>. <event>I then switched my phone to
            video camera mode and filmed the object for approx fourty seconds</event>. As I was
        filming, the object looked as though it was beginning to <ufoDesc>back away from us whilst
            getting slightly higher in the sky and at this same time it was also reducing in
            size</ufoDesc> . <ufoDesc>When the object reached about half the size it was when we
            originally spotted it an aircraft appeared from my right hand side</ufoDesc> and
        appeared to be heading in the direction of the object whilst giving it a wide berth. A few
        seconds later <ufoDesc>the object reduced to a pin point of light and then completely
            disappeared from view</ufoDesc>. On arrival back home <event>I took out my mobile phone
            and the film I had taken of the object was gone but the photo I had taken remained
            intact</event>. On viewing the photo the <ufoDesc>ball of light</ufoDesc> can be clearly
        seen. There are a number of stars in the photo so establishing wether this object should
        have been there or not should be easily calculable as there are several points of reference
        within the photo and the exact time and date is known. Unfortunately I am having problems
        attaching the photo to this mail at this time.</body>
    <signature>Many thanks []</signature>


</report>
