<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2460_pg189">

    <head><eventName>VAP/UFO SIGHTING REPORT</eventName>. For Air Sec. 2a.</head>

    <body><eventDate date="6/2/2009">6/2/2009</eventDate>: approx. <weather>17:30</weather>.
            <event>Duration: approx. 5 mins</event>. Weather: <weather>fine</weather>; > <weather>15
            miles visibility</weather>; <weather>wind speed - 1 knot</weather>; <weather>cloudless
            to horizon</weather>; <weather>temp. approx. freezing</weather>, moon and Jupiter
        (latter 180 deg. from object) <weather>clear / no distortion</weather>. Direction of first sighting approx. ENE
        of witness, last sighting approx. 90 deg. in WNW direction relative to witness position;
        <ufoDesc>speed estimated at less than 15mph</ufoDesc>. Distance to object approx, 1 mile at first sighting and
        approx. 15 deg. above horizon; object appeared to follow vertical contours of land, ie.
        gentle undulation, course appeared to be a straight line, i.e. no horizontal deviation
        apparent. <ufoDesc>Object was a clearly defined</ufoDesc> (<ufoDesc>no diffuse edges</ufoDesc>), <ufoDesc>shiny</ufoDesc> (<ufoDesc>reflected light only, no
        evidence of light emission from the object</ufoDesc>), <ufoDesc>silvery, metallic cylinder with rounded ends</ufoDesc>
        and, when compared to sizes of trees in approx. vicinity of object, was <ufoDesc>roughly 50 feet in
        length</ufoDesc>. <ufoDesc>No distinguishing features</ufoDesc> other than a small area in the <ufoDesc>lower midsection that
        appeared slightly darker/matt relative to the rest of the body and a small, solid protrusion
        on the upper rear' body</ufoDesc> (relative to direction off light) - stated as not looking like an
        aircraft tail (wrong shape and too small to be an aerodynamic control surface-<event> witness used
        to civilian and military aircraft types</event>): <ufoDesc>no markings of any kind and no lights</ufoDesc>. <ufoDesc>No sound
        from object, nor emissions seen (exhaust, etc.)</ufoDesc>, <ufoDesc>though high flying aircraft could be
        faintly heard shortly after the sighting</ufoDesc> in the opposite part of the sky to said sighting
        and at far greater distance than the object (the witness lives under the main high altitude
        civilian north-south air route and the low altitude military corridor, sounds from the
        latter can be heard for many miles, even in windy weather). At last sight it was seen almost
        from directly behind, remaining <ufoDesc>shiny/metallic, clearly defined, having no protuberances</ufoDesc> (<ufoDesc>no
        sign of horizontal tail or wing structures</ufoDesc>- the 'rear' structure seen from the side was
        sufficiently small/blunt that it barely appeared above the rim of the body), <ufoDesc>no rear
        aperlures (exhaust nozzles)</ufoDesc> and again <ufoDesc>no signs of exhaust, or atmospheric
            distortion/turbulance</ufoDesc> noted: <ufoDesc>the rear was circular in shape</ufoDesc> (e.g. rear end of a uniform,
        closed cylinder). Location of sighting: first seen in the area between <eventLocation eloc="Mealrigg">Mealrigg</eventLocation> (postcode of
        which is [] and [] and Langrigg and finished by heading through direction of Silloth
        Cumbria. Witness location was field to SE ( 200 yards from house) - interviewer taken to
        exact site and details pointed out. Conclusion of witness (aged 25) and interviewer
        (father): <ufoDesc>solid craft under control bearing no similarity to any known terrestrial aircraft</ufoDesc>
        and <ufoDesc>exhibiting an ability to maintain a constant height above the ground at a speed which
        would not allow any normal propulsion system or aerodynamic structure to maintain lift</ufoDesc>,
        other than such as <event>VSTOL type aircraft and balloons (both definitely ruled out)</event>. <event>Definitely
        not astronomical or meteorological phenomenon</event>. [Sketch of craft provided by witness - side
        view: height/diameter appears from sketch to be approx. 1/5 or 1/6 that of the length.] </body>

    <signature>Witness [] Interviewer [] Aspatria, Wigton, Cumbria CA7 3LE.</signature>



</report>
