<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2462_Report_pg157">
    <head>Sent: 1 6 July 2009 17:45 T o : Air CmdSecCS-UFO Desk1 Subject: <eventName>Dancing
            Lights</eventName></head>
    <address>Hi.</address>
    <body><event>Over the past two weeks the same event has been witnessed by myself and my girlfriend
        twice, and a third person on a completely independant occasion.</event> Last <weather>night</weather> (<eventDate
            date="07/15/2009">15/07/09</eventDate>) at around about <weather>23.30</weather>, I
        myself any my girlfriend noticed what seemed to be a <ufoDesc>very bright white
            light</ufoDesc>. <ufoDesc>almost like a large Star</ufoDesc>, <ufoDesc>appearing to move
            slowly in the sky</ufoDesc>, north- <eventLocation eloc="Trimkey_Suffolk">West of
            Trimkey St Mary. Suffolk</eventLocation>. above the river Orwell. The <ufoDesc>Light</ufoDesc> to moved
        south, <event>doubled back on itself in a smooth motion to its original position in sky</event>, at which
        point <ufoDesc>a similar light suddenly appeared with it</ufoDesc>. T<ufoDesc>he two lights almost "danced" around each
        other, each making our one equal hall of a circle. before splitting of in completely
        opposite directions</ufoDesc>. <ufoDesc>The original light quickly veered towards our position, whilst the
        newer light moved off at speed towards the north west, away from us</ufoDesc>. At this point it became
        apparent that <ufoDesc>the lights were either moving at speed or were much lower in the air that
        first apparent</ufoDesc>. <ufoDesc>The Light cruised above us</ufoDesc>. and <ufoDesc>I noticed that unlike most aircraft there
        was only this single bright white light. no repeating flashes, or different coloured lights
        usually seen</ufoDesc>. (There were at least 3other conventional aircraft in the sky at the time with
        which to compare the object) A<event> vauge black outline could be made out surrounding the light
        against the night sky</event>. however this may have just been wishful thinking from my eyes, trying
        to imagine the shape. As I commented, there were other aircraft in the sky, and a vauge
        drone could he heard from the one closest to us. however <ufoDesc>the "Light" made absolutely no
            noise what so ever.</ufoDesc> Also in comparisons with the other aircraft. this Light was clearly
        closer to us that expected. As the Light reached almost mediately overhead. <ufoDesc>it disappeared
        instantaneously</ufoDesc>. At that point in time. there was very little cloud cover and <weather>the Stars
        could be seen clearly</weather>, so I ruled out the disruption if cloud cover. The previously <ufoDesc>bright
        white light</ufoDesc>, simply disappeared before us. Usually I would have put something such as this
        down to perhaps just a normal aircraft, a Chinese lantern or just an odd experience.
        However, as I mentioned, this is the second time in two weeks both myself and my girlfriend
        have witnessed the exact same sequence of events, over the same time scale. Last time I had
        just brushed the sighting off as "odd" We arrived at my girlfriends house, and began to tell
        her mum of what we've just seen. At which point she interrupted, stating that she had seen
        the exact same thing, with incredibly similar movements the previous week. Describing the
        "dance" as if she had seen through my own eyes. She was unaware of what we had seen, and
        visa versa. The only objects that I can think resembles the light most simply, by way of an
        explanation, are Chinese lanterns. But this wouldn't explain the "dance", or the fact the
        two moved off in opposite directions. (Particularly the one above us, moving against the
        wind). <ufoDesc>The lights were just far too bright to be a lantern</ufoDesc> my opinion. and <event>acted and looked
        so unlike conventional aircraft that I cannot think of an explanation</event>. </body>
    <signature>Yours Sincerely.</signature>
</report>
