<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2463_Report_pg78">

    <address>Hi</address>
    <body> I would like to report a UFO sighting. I organised a <eventName>BBQ for some
            friends</eventName> on <eventDate date="07/11/2009" toc="20090711">11th July 2009</eventDate> at my
        parents home in <eventLocation eloc="Palmers_Green">palmers green, North
            London</eventLocation> (n13). We live in a small row of terraced houses just off the
        A406, on a busy dual carriageway. The weather was pretty <weather>drizzly</weather> that
            <weather>evening</weather> but as i had planned it for some time. decided to go ahead.
        At the time of the sighting (think it was <weather>between 8-9 pm</weather>) i was in the
        garden with 2 friends when i saw an <ufoDesc>orange fireball about to crash</ufoDesc> 2
        gardens away (about 50m away). <event>My initial thought was it was a plane on fire about to
            crash</event>. but <event>it wasn't travelling fast enough as a crashing plane, more
            like a slow motion crash as we had time to comment on the trajectory</event>. <event>We
            all waited for the 'bang' but nothing</event>. One of my friends ran upstairs to see if
        she could see it from the bathroom... She called as it was now <ufoDesc>very high in the sky
            about 1/2 a mile away</ufoDesc>. We all went back into the garden and discussed what it
        was. we soon realised it was not any of the following • airplane/ helicopter - no noise •
        Mare / firework - <ufoDesc>no smoke</ufoDesc> and it also <ufoDesc>moved from a 30 degree
            gradient about to crash, to moving very high in the sky</ufoDesc>. • air balloon- as it
        was very close, we could see it was a <ufoDesc>pure ball of fire</ufoDesc>, also again the
        movement. Upon being in the garden, <event>again another object passed by about 3-5 minutes
            after seeing the first one</event>. This time it did not follow the 30 degree 'crashing'
        trajectory but <event>flew past a little higher but along the same path</event>, 2 gardens
        away. This time we all ran upstairs to the bathroom to get a better- further look at where
        it was going. Again it went up very high about half mile away. I ran to get my digital SLR
        camera with telescopic lense, but the camera refused to take a picture... just zooming in
        and out. again we returned to the garden, discussing what we had seen. <event>For the third
            time another object flew overhead</event>, we dashed upstairs again, again grabbing my
        camera, again unable to take a picture, so instead i grabbed my small digital camera.
            <event>I managed to capture an image of this one but not as close as i would have
            liked</event>. <ufoDesc>This object seemed to have something protruding from the main
            body</ufoDesc>. Almost like <ufoDesc>it was a spherical object on fire, but with a leg
            protruding from it, also on fire, but with a visible gap between the body and the
            leg.</ufoDesc> yet they moved together in unison as fi they were attached. <event>In
            short • we saw 3 spherical fireballs, with an orange glow • seen north London N13 •
            approx 8 9- pm saturday 11th July 2009. • 3 witnesses - no alcohol involved • all
            following same path. one almost appearing to crash before appearing higher in the sky •
            distance of 25 - 50 metres</event>.</body>
    <signature>Hope this is of some help, i would like to hear some feedback if possible. regards
        []</signature>


</report>
