<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2465_Report_pg155">
    
        <address>Hello,</address>
        
    <body> I trust that both of you are the correct personnel to help with my enquiry. If
        not I would be grateful if you would forward this email to correct personnel.
        
        <event>Please find below a UFO eye witness statement that I have submitted to the UK
        UFO SIGHTING website</event>. The first object detailed below was a helicopter,
        however, I would like you to see if you can provide any explanation or identify
        the second craft that was seen by myself on <weather>Saturday night</weather> <eventDate date="10/31/2009" toc="20091031">[3lst October 2009)</eventDate>.
        I assure you that this is not a hoax.
        
        "Incidents occurred over <eventLocation eloc="Winchburgh">Winchburgh</eventLocation>, West Lothian between 7.30 to 8.30 pm
        - two incidents are described, one was definately a helicopter but the other
        craft could not be identified.
        
        The two events happened within an hour - <event>at about 7.30pm heard rapid approach
        of a helicopter</event> - could have been Police chopper as I have seen this flying
        over area but usually during daytime. It finally came into view (standing in my
        back garden which faces west) and heard / saw obvious chopper but could not
        distinguish make. <ufoDesc>Engine sounded different to police chopper</ufoDesc> although it was
        flying much lower than normal. Saw <ufoDesc>navigation lights</ufoDesc> and curiously the <ufoDesc>whole
        underside of the helicopter cabin was illuminated in a white light</ufoDesc> (was not the
        searchlight - this was actual underside of craft that was illuminated). This
        passed over and flew away flying generally from west to east. Came inside, had
        dinner then after clearing up went outside again for some fresh air and glad I
        did.
        
        An object, <ufoDesc>flying VERY low</ufoDesc>, came into view about three houses along to my
        right. I could not make out full body but using red lights it seemed to be
        <ufoDesc>cylindrical and as wide as an ordinary helicopter</ufoDesc>. This object came from south
        east flying in general direction of north west toward Blackness / River Forth.
        Three things I noted : (1) <ufoDesc>it was totally silent</ufoDesc>, (2) <ufoDesc>it had two large red
        navigation lights on body with one on top and other on bottom but placed      
        diagonally opposite each other</ufoDesc> i.e. bottom left and top right from angle I was
        viewing object, and (3) <ufoDesc>was moving VERY slowly, infact, almost drifting</ufoDesc>. Object
        in full view (at an angle) for only about
        8 seconds. Regretted not driving to chase object as i had went upstairs to rear
        bedroom to see if i could gain a better view. By this time object had gone
        behind trees on the small west facing embankment but could still see the
        <ufoDesc>flashing red strobe lights</ufoDesc> - one strobe went then the other went off in a
        repeated set design (i.e. <ufoDesc>lights did not operate randomly</ufoDesc>). Object was then
        lost from view. Would like to state that it could not have been a plane as it
        would have stalled due to the very low speed (<ufoDesc>estimated 5 to 10 mph</ufoDesc>).
        Helicopter possible but why no noise - not aware that choppers can be slienced
        at such a low altitude, as object could only have been a couple of hundred feet
        off the ground..... if that {note it came in very low, just above double storey
        rooftop level). <ufoDesc>There was no noise, no vibration and no electro-magnetic
        interference</ufoDesc> as far as 1 could see (house lights stayed on, did not flicker etc).
        
        Noted on other recent reports that drones (presume man made unmanned 
        aircraft) were reported in skies above <location loc="Edinburgh">Edinburgh</location> area and this is a
        possibility, but why fly them at such a low altitude and over populated areas?
        There was no further sign of the chopper after this incident, but noted a
        commercial aircraft on final approach to Edinburgh Airport coming in from
        roughly the southwest may have had object in sight. Have emailed <eventName>Edinburgh
        Airport</eventName> and <organization org="RAF_Leuchars">RAF Leuchars</organization> to see if they can shed any light on this incident." </body>
        
        <signature>With thanks,
         []</signature>
   
        
    
    
</report>

