<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2623_Report_pg197">
    
    <head>12 Dec 2007</head> 
        
    <address>Dear Sir/Madam</address>
        
    <body>I am writing to you in regards to an unusual aerial observation that I
        witnessed on Saturday the <eventDate date="10/20/2007"> 20 October 2007</eventDate> at 12.10 pm above my fathers home,
        which is situated on the outskirts of <eventLocation eloc="Portsmouth">Portsmouth</eventLocation> below portsdown hill.
        Just after midday at 12.10 pm I observed from my fathers back garden an unusual
        <ufoDesc>oval/spherical shaped</ufoDesc> object that appeared to cross the flight path of a commercial
        aircraft, narrowly missing it, <event>as the <ufoDesc>oval/spherical object</ufoDesc> approached the aircraft it
        appeared to <ufoDesc>accelerate very fast</ufoDesc>, in doing so it appeared to <ufoDesc>wobble from side to side</ufoDesc></event> as
        <event>it passed directly in front of the commercial aircraft narrowly avoiding a collision</event>, I
        briefly watched the object move off to the east before deciding to rush back in to my
        fathers home to retrieve my camcorder, but unfortunately when I returned to the
        garden the object was no longer visible, (see drawing enclosed, Attachment 1!)
        However within 2 minutes I sighted and managed to film on my camcorder another
        object in the sky roughly in the same vicinity as the previous occurrence that I
        couldn’t identify (see pictures enclosed, Attachment 2) the <event>object remained virtually
        stationary throughout the duration of 10 mimutes until it finally disappeared in to the
        clouds</event>.
        
        Mr Alan Hubrecht who is a Belgium national and a “<organization org="NATO">NATO</organization> expert in peace support
        operations and critical infrastructure projection” wrote on my behalf to <organization org="Airprox">Airprox</organization>
        concerning this incident, <organization org="Airprox">Airprox</organization> passed on the information to the <organization org="CAA">CAA</organization> (see
        enclosed; Mr Hubrecht’s initial request to <organization org="Airprox">Airprox</organization> (Attachment 3) and the <organization org="CAA">CAA’s</organization>
        reply back to Mr Hubrecht concerning the radar data, Attachment 4). </body>
        
        <signature>Mr Hubrecht has asked if he could communicate with you directly concerning this
        incident,
        Is this possible?
        
        I would be grateful for your help in this matter.
        Yours sincerely
        []</signature>

    
    
</report>