<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2625_Report_pg193">
    
    <address>
        inforequest: hello
    </address>
    
    <body>
        I was in my garden smoking a fag... Im not allowed to smoke in the house... and
        looking at the sky... there was some <weather>cloud cover</weather> just like a <weather>high fog</weather>. Athough this
        was not dense. I could see <ufoDesc>2 stars</ufoDesc>, whilst i was looking at the 2 stars that i could
        see, a <ufoDesc>white with a tint of orange light</ufoDesc> came into view over the top of my neighbours
        house it was traveling in a westerly but slightly south direction at a medium speed,
        but faster than the jets that come over my house from <eventLocation eloc="Gatwick_Airport">gatwick airport</eventLocation>. This star !
        light ! UFO ! <event>travelled in a perfectly straight line at the same altitude as the cloud
        cover maybe a little higher</event>, there was <ufoDesc>no sound at all completly silent</ufoDesc>. I watched it
        for as long at i could untill it dissapeared into the the cloud, and i could no longer
        see it. I was then thinking to myself what the heck was that !! I had no explination.
        I then was looking at the <eventName>2 stars</eventName> that I was origonaily looking at... but at that
        moment the star that was the lowest (or the furthest)
        away from me, <event>suddenly started moving in the same direction allthough it was not
        taking the same path it was heading to the same point as the lst</event> (<ufoDesc>light, star, UFO</ufoDesc>,)
        this one was travelling at a <ufoDesc>much slower speed</ufoDesc>. I also watched this one untill i
        could see it no more at the same point as the first, This one also made <ufoDesc>no sound</ufoDesc> and  
        was at about the same altitude if not maybe a little higher than the 1st.... Then I
        didnt know what to do !!! I know what i saw.. so i tried to contact <organization org="ATC">ATC gatwick</organization> they
        gave me a phone number that is now not in use.... I then phoned <organization org="Sussex_Police">sussex police</organization> and
        told them what i had seen thay gave me a reference number :1907/<eventDate  date="01/06/2008" toc="20080106">1/6/2008</eventDate>
        they then gave me the <organization org="MOD">MOD UFO</organization> sighting number whitch then took me te a awnsering
        machine and i left a message. I had had no reply I know that 4 at least 4 other people
        saw these stars UFO's lights in worthing because they called the local radio station
        (splash FM).... 
        I would love to hear some feedback from this.      
        I know that we are not alone, the universe is to varst to even think that we are... If
        I can be a help or a use to you please do not hesitate to contact me... trust me i       
        will not be alarmed... look forward to hearing from you.</body>
        
        <signature>many thanks  
        []</signature>
    
</report>
