<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="../Schema/Report_Schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>

<report id="2625_Report_pg103">
    
    <head>From: []
        To: newsdesk@kendal.newsquest.co.uk
        Subject: [] RE: UFOs
        Date: <eventDate date="06/24/2008">Tue, 24 Jun 2008</eventDate> 14:42:12 +0100 </head>
    
    
        <address>Dear []</address>
        
       <body>My name is [] I am 19 and in Kendal. I have seen these <ufoDesc>orange
        lights</ufoDesc> in the sky on two occassions (see below) since Friday, and I can say
        with absolute certainty that these are not sateliltes, space debris or the
        ISS.

        The first sighting was looking west of<eventLocation eloc="Kendal">Kendal</eventLocation> at around <weather>11pm</weather> on Friday
        night. Quite low was a <ufoDesc>bright red/orange light</ufoDesc> which I assumed was a
        light of a communications antenna but then realised there aren't any in
        that area so I stopped and watched it. I then thought It must be a red
        flare, but a few seconds later a <event>bright, phosphorus white light fell from
        the orange one, and drifted siowly towards the ground before
        disappearing</event>. As soon as the white light disappeared the red one slowly
        faded out. The red light was <ufoDesc>completly static</ufoDesc> throughout the 10-15 second
        sighting.
        
        This sighting was not enough to make me want fo email the Gazette, as I
        thought there must be a logical explanation for it. However last night my
        girlfriend came running into the house, in <eventLocation eloc="Kendal">Kendal</eventLocation>, and told me and my
        brother to come outside (at around <weather>11.15pm</weather>). She said she had just seen
        an <ufoDesc>orange star</ufoDesc> move from it’s place in the sky, <event>dart across in a straight
        line and then do a NINETY DEGREES TURN before stopping</event>. How many
        satellites can do this? We stared at it, and realised there were 3 other dim
        orange lights, and they were constantly moving in a formation, as if they
        were trying to find the correct position. <event>They came very close together,
        then very far apart, the one on the left went from the top of the triangle
        (the shape they had formed) to the bottom within 2 or 3 seconds</event>. The
        lights finally settled in an <ufoDesc>arrow shape</ufoDesc>, ie:
        
        
        We watched for half an hour, but they weren't moving very much after
        that, but we noticed a new dimmer light above and to the right of the left
        light.
      
        
        This new dimmer one moved alot, and the bottom right one started
        moving more too. 
        
        Our necks were hurting and we'd been staring for half an hour so we
        went outside, as they didn’t seem to be moving any more. I went back
        out 5 minutes later to check up and they'd formed like this
        
        
        This is not an exaggeration, and I wouldn't have e-mailed if I didn't see
        this for such a long period last night. I hope with all the reports you are
        getting you can let me know if anyone else saw either of the sightings, so
        I don't think I'm going insane! The fact that my girlfriend saw a <event>light do a
        right-angle turn</event> proves [] can't dismiss these sightings as space
        shuttles or satellites. </body>

        <signature>Regards
        []</signature>

</report>